OYEGUNLE DANIEL OLUWADAMILOLA

Mowe, Ogun State • ddoyegunle@gmail.com • +234 907 905 2910

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Religion and Peace Studies graduate with a strong understanding of modern teaching methods. I consider myself to be a very analytical, goal-oriented, dedicated, and hardworking person.

I am a meticulous individual who can easily adapt to all managerial responsibilities and provide administrative assistance. Along with taking responsibility for my own tasks and ensuring that the company's objectives are met, I enjoy working with others. I'm a Data Analyst with a keen eye for detail and a passion for uncovering insights from data to drive informed decision-making.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MCPHERSON University (NYSC)

Seriki Sotayo, Ogun State

SECRETARY TO THE DEAN OF STUDENT AFFAIRS

November 2022 - November 2023

- Answered phones, took messages, and handled correspondence.
- Organizing appointments and maintaining diaries.
- Reports were typed, prepared, and compiled.
- Communicated with relevant organizations and clients.
- Worked as a receptionist and/or met and greeted customers.
- Workloads are prioritized.

City Campus Academy

Ofada, Ogun State

TEACHER

September 2017 - July 2018

- Worked cooperatively with other teachers, administrators, and parents to help students reach learning objectives.
- Plan and execute educational in-class and outdoor activities and events.
- Assess and record students' progress and provide grades and feedback.
- Kept students on-task with proactive behavior modification and positive reinforcement strategies.
- Created and distributed progress reports to both students and parents.

Leadway Assurance

Mowe, Ogun State

SALES EXCUTIVE

2016 - 2017

- To increase customer acquisition levels, leads were generated and appropriate solutions were provided to customers.
- Customers' needs were assessed, and assistance and product information were provided.
- Obtaining deposits and remaining balances from clients.
- Prepared weekly and monthly reports.
- Met or exceeded sales goals.

Devine Styles Studio

Redemption City, Ogun State

STUDIO AND AFFAIRS MANAGER

2015 - 2016

- Managed bookkeeping, sales, marketing, purchasing, training and hiring.
- Created innovating ways to increase sales.
- Technically proficient in camera equipment, film, lenses, filters, and lighting.
- Retouched images and color corrected to more closely match item to screen.
- Photographed fashion items for marketing and online sales.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

McPherson University, Seriki Sotayo, Ogun State

Bachelor of Arts (B.A) in Religion and Peace Studies October 2018 – July 2022

Grade: Second-Class Honors

Codar Tech Africa, Wemabod Estate Ikeja, Lagos State

Data Analytics January 2024 – April 2024

CORE SKILLS

- Communication skills.
- Microsoft Office.
- Adaptability.
- Teamwork.
- Goal oriented.
- Problem solving.
- Time management.
- Good management skills.

PROJECT WORKED ON

EXCEL

SUPER STORE DATA:

I analyzed data from a superstore. I explored specifics areas of the store. For example, I
looked at sales, inventory, customer behavior, the total profit and sales over the months,
the total profit earned by category, the total sales by category, identified any seasonal
patterns or trends, top 5 sub-category by sales and also explored the distribution of sales
and profits

POWER BI

CAR SALES DATA REPORT:

In Power BI, worked on analyzing car sales data. I created excellent interactive reports
and visualizations. I built the dashboards and created insights related to car sales trends,
regional performance, or customer preferences.

MYSOL

BANK DATABASE CREATION AND ANALYSIS:

 I created a bank database using MySQL. I design the schema, set up tables, and define relationships. I performed various kinds of analysis. Examples include transaction patterns, account balances, or loan approvals.

CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS

- National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) Discharge Certificate October 2023
- Global Leadership Summit May 2022
- Certificate of Achievement May 2022
- Certificate Of Commendation June 2022
- Certificate of Meritorious Service June 2022
- Certificate of Excellence June 2021
- Certificate of Attendance June 2020
- Certificate of Achievement June 2019
- Most Promising Writer of the Year December 2019
- Certificate of Recognition January 2015
- Timber Entrepreneurial December 2015
- Award of excellence, McPherson University Chapel of Praise 2022
- Outstanding Leadership Award, McPherson University Chapel of Praise 2022
- Impact Award, College of Humanities, Social and Management Science McPherson University - 2022
- Excellence Award, College of Humanities Students 'Association, McPherson University 2021
- Press Board Recognition Award 2019 Most Promising Writer 2019

HOBBIES

- Writing.
- Reading.
- Traveling.
- Volunteering.
- Teaching.
- Movies & Music's.

REFERENCES

Rev. Frank Oluwadelemi

Foursquare Gospel Church Adesan-Mowe, Ogun State Tel: 08033341264

Mr. Ayotunde Eniola

Head HR and Admin Chartered Institute of Directors, Nigeria.

Tel: 08146484077

Dr. Austin Omomia

H.O.D Religion and Peace McPherson University Seriki Sotayo, Ogun State, Nigeria.

Tel: 08033031035

Mrs. Oluwaponmile Adeyemo

Director of Education

Trinity International College, Ofada, Ogun State, Nigeria. Tel: 08034242339